<?xml version="1.0"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">

<channel>

<title>The Alex Jones Show - Infowars.com</title>
<itunes:subtitle>Because there's a war on for your mind!</itunes:subtitle>
<link>http://www.infowars.com</link>
<itunes:summary> Because there's a war on for your mind; veteran broadcaster, filmmaker and media analyst Alex Jones brings you incredible interviews with people on the frontlines of the Infowar and takes an in-depth look at the news between the day's headlines.</itunes:summary>
<description>Because there's a war on for your mind; broadcaster, filmmaker and news analyst Alex Jones brings you an in-depth look at the news between the day's headlines.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 01:00:00 -0000</lastBuildDate>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Alex Jones</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>sysadmin_xml3_nospam@infowars.com</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<webMaster>sysadmin_xml3_nospam@infowars.com</webMaster>
<ttl>250</ttl>

<itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics" />

<itunes:image href="http://www.infowars.com/images2/activism/podcast_ajshow_150.jpg"/>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-20, Thursday</title>
<description>to be added...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180920_Thu_Alex.mp3" length="57568531" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180920_Thu_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-19, Wednesday</title>
<description>Chaos Supreme - The woman who accused President Trump’s Supreme Court nominee of sexual assault wants her allegations investigated by the FBI before she testifies at next week’s Senate Judiciary Committee. Additionally, Senator Dianne Feinstein said the Senate hearing should be delayed to allow a proper investigation and the SCOTUS pick, Brett Kavanaugh, is reportedly ready to testify that he was not at the high school party in question. Trump said it would be “wonderful” if Kavanaugh’s accuser showed up for Monday’s scheduled hearing that media is already gearing up as a spectacle to rival the Clarence Thomas and Anita Hill saga. Joining today’s show is Senate candidate Joey Gibson explaining his pro-American journey.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180919_Wed_Alex.mp3" length="57567906" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180919_Wed_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-18, Tuesday</title>
<description>This year’s Emmys awards show achieved record low ratings all while more Americans begin to turn off the TV. Also, President Trump has ordered the release of key documents regarding the FISA court warrant on Carter Page, all reports of FBI interviews with Bruce Our, as well as “the release of all text messages relating to the Russia investigation, without redaction, of James Comey, Andrew McCabe, Peter Strzok, Lisa Page, and Bruce Ohr.” Joining today’s show in-studio is comedian Owen Benjamin discussing how the establishment left ruined comedy. Furthermore, Tommy Robinson returns to share the latest from Europe.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180918_Tue_Alex.mp3" length="57567484" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180918_Tue_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-17, Monday</title>
<description>SCOTUS nominee Brett Kavanaugh is set to refute an accusation of a sexual assault that allegedly occurred when he was in highschool in the early 1980s. Kavanaugh’s accuser, now a professor and donor to the DNC, said she thought Kavanaugh was going to “inadvertently” kill her. Also, the death toll of Hurricane Florence reached 16 and worse flooding is predicted as multiple rivers are filling past the bursting point. Joining today’s show is Attorney-at-Law Tyler Nixondiscussing the left’s assault on the liberty of all Americans. Start your week informed. Call and tune in now!</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180917_Mon_Alex.mp3" length="57567691" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180917_Mon_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-16, Sunday</title>
<description>Dems Blame Florence on Trump - Hurricane Florence swept through the Carolinas over the weekend, bringing destruction and floodwaters to the region, and Democrats are blaming Trump for the storm. The now-tropical depression prompted hundreds of rescues from the Cajun Navy, Coast Guard, and other brave volunteers. Meanwhile, in typical fake news fashion, The Weather Channel and CNN have been busy playing up the intensity of the storm to boost ratings. On today’s show, we’ll talk about the Trump administration’s response to the storm, and more!</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180916_Sun_Alex.mp3" length="28779288" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180916_Sun_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-14, Friday</title>
<description>Hurricane Florence’s Friday impact knocked out power to half a million homes and businesses while delivering a storm surge of atleast 11 feet in some areas. The “biblical” storm ripped apart buildings and sent pieces flying. The now Category 1 hurricane has already prompted harrowing rescues from brave workers and volunteers. Joining today’s show is Benghazi hero Kris &quot;Tanto&quot; Paronto revealing the hottest DC happenings and the latest geopolitical news. Start your weekend informed.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180914_Fri_Alex.mp3" length="57563825" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180914_Fri_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-13, Thursday</title>
<description>Forecasts show Hurricane Florence is trending south and prompting two more states to declare a state of emergency. Thehurricane’s uncertain path has sparked evacuation and prep efforts across the entire US Southeast coast as the storm surge remains a “catastrophic” threat despite its peak winds falling to Category 3 strength. Also, a 36-year executive producer at CBS was fired allegedly over the contents of a text message. Joining today’s show in-studio is Wall Street’s Conrad Padilla providing powerful insights of network marketing. Furthermore, former liberal and founder of #WalkAway Brandon Straka shares his mission to wake up the masses duped by leftism.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180913_Thu_Alex.mp3" length="57567904" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180913_Thu_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-12, Wednesday</title>
<description>Open Season on GOP - A 35-year-old leftist was arrested for assaulting a Republican Congressional candidate with a knife just weeks before the midterm elections. Moreover, establishment media giant CNN failed to report on the attempted stabbing. On the US East Coast, major highways have been converted to one-way evacuation routes as Hurricane Florence is set to drench the Carolinas with 80-foot waves. Joining today’s show is the “civilized barbarian” Roosh Valizadeh discussing Amazon banning his book and the left’s attack on masculinity. Also, The Daily Ledger host Graham Ledger holds President Trump accountable to the Constitution while analyzing liberals’ meltdown over Trump. Special in-studio guest is CRTV host Eric Bolling discussing DC culture and the anonymous New York Times op-ed</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180912_Wed_Alex.mp3" length="57567697" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180912_Wed_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-11, Tuesday</title>
<description>Today marks the 17th year after one of America’s darkest days. The country still has yet to learn the full truth behind the 9/11 attacks. Also, Hurricane Florence’s impact will reportedly be “extremely dangerous” as authorities urge locals on the US East coast to plan ahead. Meteorologists predict a Category 4 impact later this week with winds of 130 mph. Joining today’s show is the host of Ground Zero Clyde Lewis providing cutting-edge takes on phenomena the establishment doesn’t want you to talk about.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180911_Tue_Alex.mp3" length="57568320" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180911_Tue_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-10, Monday</title>
<description>Hurricane Florence is projected to be a Category 4 hurricane by its Thursday landfall into the Southeast US coast. Authorities urge people in North Carolina and South Carolina to be vigilant and plan ahead. Also, almost 17 years after the 9/11 attack on the World Trade Center, Al-Qaeda is reportedly stronger than ever with over 20 thousand soldiers in Syria and Yemen alone. Across the Atlantic, UK opponent of PM Theresa May claims her new Brexit plan is “wrapping a suicide vest around Britain.”Joining today’s show is former liberal and founder of #WalkAway Brandon Straka sharing his mission to wake up the masses duped by leftism</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180910_Mon_Alex.mp3" length="57542508" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180910_Mon_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-09, Sunday</title>
<description>US Strikes Syria - The US military has begun airstrikes in Syria, following President Trump’s warning to Bashar al-Assad not to strike the Idlib region. Russia has vowed to retaliate if any US airstrikes took place, claiming the White Helmets group was readying a chemical weapons false flag to justify an attack. Meanwhile, Apple removed the Infowars App from its store in an unprecedented act of digital martial law. On today’s show, we’ll discuss how President Trump can avoid another World War what he can do to stop the globalist’s designs on the Middle East.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180909_Sun_Alex.mp3" length="28784199" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180909_Sun_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-07, Friday</title>
<description>President Trump’s America-first agenda blew analyst’s expectations away after delivering over 200,000 jobs last month as well as facilitating a wage increase and a generational low unemployment rate. Also, the NFL’s season opener suffered a multi-year low rating shortly after apparel titan Nike endorsed a non-athlete that even had Trump ask “what was Nike thinking?” Far south, Brazil’s presidential front-runner, who locals call their “Trump,” delivered an optimistic hospital message after surviving a stab wound from an alleged socialist. Joining today’s show is Senate challenger Shiva Ayyadurai to discuss his fight against leftists disrupting his campaign. Furthermore, Dr. Steve Pieczenik shares his powerful insight into the Deep State, Trump's foreign policy, and Big Tech’s censorship endgame.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180907_Fri_Alex.mp3" length="57567900" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180907_Fri_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-06, Thursday</title>
<description>President Trump hinted at declassifying information to expose the alleged White House saboteur who penned the New York Times op-ed promising to thwart parts of his agenda and undermine the will of the electorate. Trump called the author “gutless” and said the NYT must reveal the person for the sake of national security. Furthermore, the op-ed actually reveals the presence of the unelected deep state desperately fighting against Trump’s swamp-draining, America first agenda.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180906_Thu_Alex.mp3" length="57568113" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180906_Thu_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-05, Wednesday</title>
<description>Alex Jones storms the Washington D.C. swamp to hold the establishment media and Big Tech accountable by facing his accusers who collude to deplatform and unperson him. Catch Alex ring the alarm over Google and Apple using Communist Chinese tactics to censor political dissidents. The Infowars message to President Trump is to use Section 2 of the Sherman Antitrust Act to enforce the First Amendment and stop Big Tech’s criminal collusion of violating the civil rights of Americans. Do not miss once-in-a-lifetime press conferences where Alex calls a member of the press “dumber than a box of rocks.”</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180905_Wed_Alex.mp3" length="57538338" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180905_Wed_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-04, Tuesday</title>
<description>Alex Jones breaks down the massive lies perpetuated by the mainstream media in the wake of his internet purge, and he proves the statistics are on our side in the information war as support for the Infowars site surges in the face of big tech. Owen Shroyer joins Alex to officially announce the launch of an all new Infowars Army, and Paul Joseph Watson hosts the final hour.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180904_Tue_Alex.mp3" length="57567902" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180904_Tue_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-03, Monday</title>
<description>Rebroadcast - August  28, 2018</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180903_Mon_Alex.mp3" length="57560272" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180903_Mon_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Sep-02, Sunday</title>
<description>McCain Funeral Becomes Politicized - The memorial service of the late Sen. John McCain devolved into a Trump-bashing event, with former presidents and even McCain’s daughter throwing shade at the president during the eulogy. Meanwhile, Trump is laying the groundwork for an improved trade deal with Mexico and Canada, but Trump says Canada still needs to get its act together before coming to the table. Meanwhile, the Deep State is preparing to make big waves before the midterms, possibly readying indictments against Roger Stone and Don Jr. On today’s show, we’ll discuss how to fight back against Big Tech censorship and establishment efforts to unseat the president.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180902_Sun_Alex.mp3" length="28509286" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180902_Sun_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Aug-31, Friday</title>
<description>NBC Caught in Scandal - NBC News is under fire after multiple news article claim the network kept the Weinstein story hidden from the public. Also, Trump' s legal team is now questioning the legitimacy of Robert Mueller's broad probe and Roger Stone joins the show to talk about how he's being targeted by Mueller's team. Also, conservative activist Will Johnson explains the desperate attempt by Democrats to derail Trump's success with the job market and more.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180831_Fri_Alex.mp3" length="57559436" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180831_Fri_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Aug-30, Thursday</title>
<description>Farewell Snub - Deceased Senator John McCain’s former running mate, Sarah Palin, has been excluded from his funeral and reportedly told to stay away from the ceremony. Palin joins President Trump on the list of people barred from McCain’s funeral. Also, Trump conducted a lengthy tweet salvo against the fake establishment media saying they are the “enemy of the people” while adding, “truth doesn’t matter to them.” Joining today’s show is the grassroots director of Liberty Hangout Kaitlin Bennett explaining her expertise in spreading a conservative message amid Big Tech’s censoring. </description>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180830_Thu_Alex.mp3" length="57567695" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180830_Thu_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Aug-29, Wednesday</title>
<description>Anonymous News - After CNN’s Trump Tower story imploded due to Michael Cohen’s own lawyer admitted to being the anonymous source while also stating in the same story he declined to comment, President Trump warned Americans to keep an eye out for “anonymous sources” because it's a powerful tool of the fake news industry that he emphasizes is the “enemy of the people!” Also, Trump is ready to fight back against the collaborated efforts of the Big Tech censors targeting conservative voices. Joining today’s show is Wall Street’s Conrad Padilla providing powerful insights of network marketing. Furthermore, political cartoonist Ben Garrison shares his unique take on the Trump Admin and the state of political correctness. </description>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180829_Wed_Alex.mp3" length="57567383" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180829_Wed_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Aug-28, Tuesday</title>
<description>Rigged! - President Trump slammed Google’s biased search results that artificially boost leftist news with overwhelmingly negative links. Also, Michael Cohen’s own lawyer admits he was the anonymous source for CNN’s Trump Tower story that spurred a media circus Americans endured for months, he also regrets lying about his involvement. Furthermore, the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq each hit record highs after Trump announced the new US-Mexico Trade Agreement. Joining today’s show is Ann Coulter breaking down how exactly the Trump-hating left lost its collective mind. Our in-studio guest is founder/director of Defense Distributed Cody Wilson explaining his groundbreaking legal battle regarding the blueprints for his 3-D printed gun.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180828_Tue_Alex.mp3" length="57567170" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180828_Tue_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Aug-27, Monday</title>
<description>Stocks reached a record-high amid the United States and Mexico drawing closer to a new deal on NAFTA. The Nasdaq Composite reached 8,000 for the first time as tensions with the southern neighbor have improved. President Trump added to the anticipation by tweeting “a big deal looking good with Mexico!” Joining today’s show is Dr. Keith Moeller explaining the proven health benefits of silver technologies.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180827_Mon_Alex.mp3" length="57567482" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180827_Mon_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Aug-26, Sunday</title>
<description>Top neocon Senator John McCain passed away after a months-long battle with a brain tumor. Colleagues from both sides of the aisle - and even George Soros - have expressed their grief over the passing of the veteran and failed presidential candidate. Meanwhile, Pope Francis has been accused of covering up for the ongoing pedophile scandal unfolding in the Church, and calls for his resignation are growing.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180826_Sun_Alex.mp3" length="28784722" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180826_Sun_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alex Jones - 2018-Aug-24, Friday</title>
<description>President Trump provided Attorney General Jeff Sessions a public ultimatum to go after real corruption on the other side of the political aisle; the extensive list of viable targets included Clinton’s emails, the Steele dossier, and Russian collusion by the Dems. Trump added that the country is waiting for him to do his job and said: “Come on Jeff, you can do it.” Joining today’s show is Simon Roche of @suidlanders discussing the crisis in South Africa. Furthermore, co-founder of The Academy of AntiAging Medicine Dr. Giampapa explains the portal for stem cell therapy.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 22:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<enclosure url="http://rss.infowars.com/20180824_Fri_Alex.mp3" length="57567377" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<guid>http://rss.infowars.com/20180824_Fri_Alex.mp3</guid>
</item>

<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
</channel>

</rss>
